# Guilherme Avila

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

**E**mail

Github

Portfolio

guilhermeavila.dev

github.com/terrykrom

Guilherme Avila

### **TECHNOLOGIES**

Javascript (ES7) HTML5 NodeJS LWC

React JS CSS3 MySQL Python

React Native Apex Next JS Tailwind CSS

### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

I am passionate about building modern and intuitive digital solutions, from sleek, responsive websites to engaging mobile applications. I enjoy working with technologies like React, Next.js, and React Native to turn ideas into reality and improve user experiences.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Salesforce Developer Trainee

2024 - Currently

Full-cycle developer specializing in enterprise applications, leveraging Apex and LWC on the Salesforce platform.

IT Technician Trainee

2023 - 2024

Manutenção de computadores e dispositivos, configuração e manutenção do windows, resolução de problemas.

Desenvolvedor Freelance

2022 - Atualmente

Criação de sites, landing pages e layouts com design moderno e responsivo.

## **EDUCATION AND COURSES**

Scientific Computing with Python

2023 - 2023

FreeCodeCamp

Algorithms and Data Structures with Javascript

2023 - 2023

FreeCodeCamp

**Backend Devlopment and APIs** 

2023 - 2023

FreeCodeCamp

High School and Technician in Systems Development

2022 - 2024

Etec de Praia Grande